<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital &amp; Technical Marketing for Agencies | Always Optimizing</title>
    <link>http://elyasimukka.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Digital &amp; Technical Marketing for Agencies | Always Optimizing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>

	<atom:link href="http://elyasimukka.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://elyasimukka.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://elyasimukka.com/about/</guid>
      <description>##about I&amp;rsquo;m Elya Simukka. A digital marketing consultant for agencies. Hi.
Find greater confidence in your next project when you work with me.
Agencies trust me to be a contributing partner on their most valuable work. I white label my SEO and technical marketing services to agencies that want better client outcomes.
It&amp;rsquo;s a win-win to help marketing agencies round out their client offerings with SEO services and more. Together, we can get essential work done, &amp;amp; done well.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://elyasimukka.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://elyasimukka.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>##Let’s Connect
Need technical digital marketing guidance with your agency’s marketing project? Don’t miss out on a chance to connect. Claim your complimentary 15-minute chat.
Schedule Your Meeting</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://elyasimukka.com/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://elyasimukka.com/experience/</guid>
      <description>#experience
In what can seem like an ever-evolving space, I’ve worked as a digital marketer for 9+ years. That&amp;rsquo;s ages!
I&amp;rsquo;m committed to being an effective marketer that helps you and your clients. The add-value of an experienced &amp;amp; relevant SEO consulting partner to agencies is vital.
Technical digital marketing is more than a strategy with no action or a tactic here and there.
I find my flow here.
I mix experience, curiosity and a habit of self-education to give the greatest value to clients.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://elyasimukka.com/footer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://elyasimukka.com/footer/</guid>
      <description>I share resource roundups and my musings on SEO, analytics, reporting &amp;amp; more on social media. Let’s explore the intersection of SEO and smart creativity! Follow along.
Social Media:
  icon: &amp;ldquo;linkedin&amp;rdquo; URL: &amp;ldquo;https://www.linkedin.com/in/elyasimukka&amp;quot;
  icon: &amp;ldquo;twitter&amp;rdquo; URL: &amp;ldquo;https://twitter.com/elya365&amp;quot;
  icon: &amp;ldquo;instagram&amp;rdquo; URL: &amp;ldquo;https://www.instagram.com/simukkaconsulting/&amp;quot;
  icon: &amp;ldquo;github&amp;rdquo; URL: &amp;ldquo;https://github.com/elya365&amp;quot;
  What about NAP?
Last chance! Get a free one-on-one with me, an agency-side consultant. Learn how working together to grow your client’s owned, earned, and paid digital marketing channels can set you apart from the competition.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://elyasimukka.com/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://elyasimukka.com/services/</guid>
      <description>##Services
Agencies collaborate with me to help with challenging online marketing projects. I blend with teams as a contributor and thought partner with the following services. Here&amp;rsquo;s how I compliment your team.
###Consultant Services:
  Digital Marketing Strategy
  Website Conversion Rate Optimization (CRO) &amp;amp; User Experience (UX)
  Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
 with emphasis on technical, local &amp;amp; content SEO    Analytics
  Reporting &amp;amp; Dashboards</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://elyasimukka.com/testimonials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://elyasimukka.com/testimonials/</guid>
      <description>##Testimonials
 “I have never met anyone that has such focus and dedication to a project as Elya. I have seen her manage large &amp;gt;teams, as well as plan and strategize on in-depth digital marketing campaigns.
I would highly recommend her to any professional organization.&amp;rdquo;
 Jessica Seidel Louder Than Digital, VP of Marketing
 “I worked closely with Elya and witnessed firsthand the excellence that she brings. Her attention to detail, &amp;gt;strategic thinking, drive for continuous learning and strong communication skills make her a valued asset.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://elyasimukka.com/use-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://elyasimukka.com/use-case/</guid>
      <description>Running a marketing agency is anything but boring.
You juggle prospect pitches, wrangle clients, manage team dynamics &amp;amp; calm internal fires. Work moves faster than your Twitter feed. It&amp;rsquo;s a heart-pounding business.
You might say you’re busy. (And not bored at all.)
You’re busy doing the most for your customers and your bottom line. But how do you handle projects when the work feels almost out of reach for your team specialties?</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://elyasimukka.com/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://elyasimukka.com/values/</guid>
      <description>#Values
These are the values that guide my work. Or, how I roll in my role.
 Default to Transparency    Help when I can, refer when I can’t
  Be up-front about what I do and how it’s done
  Try easier    Apply lean principles
  Work Smarter, Not Harder
   Respect &amp;amp; Empathy Are Non-negotiable
  Be an Ally for Access</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
